Guide to the James Beard Foundation Archive 1939-2008 (bulk 1990-2008) MSS.214
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Chefs
  - Kinsella, Margaret Mary, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Kirhoffer, Rebecca, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Kirk, Johnny, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Kirsch, Abigail, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Kisler, Andreas, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Kitrilakis, Sotiris and Lidia, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Klamfer, Franz, undated (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Klaskala, Gerry, 1988-2002 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Kleiman, Evan, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Klein, Jake, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Klein, Peter, 1993-2002 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Klein, Rachel, 2004-2006 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Klein, Roxanne, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Kleinberg, Neil, 1994-2005 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Kleinman, Stephen and Ian, 2000-2006 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Kelemeniuk, Thierry, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Kline, Bo, 1998-2002 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Klinger, Anna, 1999-2001 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Klitsie, Paul and Tim Cuscaden, 2002-2005 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Kloss, Marjorie, undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Kluger, Dan, 2005-2007 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Knibb, Jason, 1994-2003 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Knight, Sean, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Knops, Sarah, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Knox, Kenneth, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Kobayashi, Hiroyuki, undated (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Kobayashi, Takashi, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Koberstein, Ulrich, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Kobin, Daniel, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Kodama, Dave "D.K.", 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Kohnorst, Heidi, undated (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Kojima, Yoshinori, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Koketsu, Craig, 2002-2004 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Kolar, Larry, 1995-2002 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Komen, Brad, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Komiyama, Masami, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Konami, Sachiko, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Kong, Andy, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Koob, Sarah, undated (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Kopelow, Eric, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Korn, Keith, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Kornell, Paula, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Korney, Gregg C., undated (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Kornick, Michael, 1993-2004 (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Korycki, John and Mark Weber, 1993-1999 (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Koumbis, Jack, 1990-1999 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Koury, Matthew, 1990-2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Koval, William, 1995-2003 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Kramer, Matt, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Kramer, Michael, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Kramer, Stanley, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Krasne, Karen, 1997-2001 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kratky, David, 2003-2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Krause, Richard, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Krauss, Sibella, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Krebs, Frank, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kremezi, Aglaia, 1992-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Kretchmer, Jerome, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kreuther, Gabriel, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Krinn, Jonathan, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Krizman, Steve, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Kruger, Dan, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Kuchinskas, Jerry, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Kuettel, Ralf, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Kuhlmann, Joseph, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Kuelto, Pat, 1993-1998 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Kumin, Albert, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Kump, Christopher, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Kumpa, Lydia, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Kunz, Gray, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Kwaku-Dongo, Francois, 1996-2002 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Kwan, Alan, undated (Box 24, Folder 26a)
  - Kwong, Paul, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 26b)
  - Kyndberg, James, 1991-1998 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Laakkonen, Rick, 1992-2002 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Labrie, Alain, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Labriola, Anthony, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Lachowicz, Michael and Thomas, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Lacroix, Jean-Marie, 1992-2006 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Lacoste, Ris, 1995-2005 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Ladner, Mark, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Lagasse, Emeril, 1990-2004 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Lagay, Jean-Claude, undated (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Lage, Jason, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Lago, Pitita, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Lahey, James, 1994-2006 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Lahey, Scott, 2002-2005 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Lahm, Mark, 1991-2001 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Laird and Company, undated (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Laird, James, 1996-2004 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Laiskonis, Michael, 2002-2006 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Lake, Edward, 2004-2006 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Lake, Matthew, 1995-2007 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Lam, Noreen, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Lamas, Anthony, 2000-2007 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Lamb Hayes, Joanne, 2002-2004 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Lambert, Dorte, undated (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Lambert, Paula, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Lambing, Thomas J., 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Lamorte, Roberto, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Lancarte, Lanny, 2003-2005 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Lane, Nicole and Joseph Rodriguez, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Lanfranconi, Cesare, 2001-2004 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Lang, George, 1989-2002 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Lang, Jennifer, 1988-1991 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Lange, Frederic, 1991-2000 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Langenfeld, Mark, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Langermann, Neal, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - Langlois, Stephen, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Langton, Brenda, 1996-2000 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Lanza, Louis, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Lanzarotti, Giovanni, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Lanza, Anna Tasca, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Laprise, Normand, 1993-2000 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Larijani, Farrokh, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Larsen, Peter, undated (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Larsen, Ketil, undated (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Larson, Brian, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Larson, David, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Larson, Michela, 1987-1992 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Larson, Paul, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Larsson, Christer, 1992-2002 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Larsson, Morgan, undated (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - LaScola, Michael, 1999-2006 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Lasher, Anne Marie, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Lashley, Carl, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Laskowski, Bernard, 1999-2004 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Laslow, Eric, 1998-2003 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Lata, Michael, 1998-2004 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Latona, Steve, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Lattanzi, Paolo, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Latture, Keith, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Lau, Jacqueline, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Laurent-Perrier, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Lauvand, Remi, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Lavarra, Giuseppe, undated (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Lavazza, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Lavoie, Jeannot, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Lawrence, David, undated (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Lawrence, Mary James, undated (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Lawson, David, 1988-1994 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Lazaroff, Barbara, undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Leach, Richard, 1993-2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Leader, Daniel, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Leahy, Donna, 1991-1996 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Leal, Edgar, 2003-2007 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Leandri, Alberto, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Leary, Dennis, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Le, Hung, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lebalch, Josie, 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Lebewohl, Abe, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Lebewohl, Jack, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Lecomte, Michel, 1988-1992 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Le Croze, Gilbert, 1992-1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - LeCoze, Maguy, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - LeDily, Eric, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lee, Alex, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lee, David, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lee, Edward, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lee, Frank, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Lee, John, undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Lee, Juno, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Lee, Kenneth, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Lee, Kye Hwa, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Lee, Susur, 1988-2005 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Leeds, Jamie, 1991-2006 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Lefebvre, Bruce, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Lefebvre, Ludovic, 1998-2006 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - LeFevre, David, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Leff, Jay, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Leffler, Walter, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - LeGuelaff, Jacques, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Lehtinen, Jani, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Leibfried, Scott, 1997-2004 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Leitner, Rupert, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Lelli, Tom, 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Lemanissier, Jean-Pierre, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Len, Allison, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Lenard, Eric, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Lenchner, Dan, 1988-1997 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Lenhart, Scott, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Lentini, Guiseppe, 2001-2006 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Lentz, David, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Leo, Dario, undated (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Leon, Adrian, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Leon, Orlando, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Leonard, Edward, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Leonardi, Jacques, 1997-2002 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Leone, Ignazio, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Leong, Sam, undated (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Leong, Kenneth, undated (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Le Pape, Gwenael, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Le Rasle, Renaud, 1997-2001 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Le Rouzic, Jean, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Leroy, Dan, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - LeRoy, Warner, 1995-2001 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Letard, Christophe, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Lett, David, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Leu, Christoph, undated (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Leung, Henry, 1991-2001 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Levin, Carrie, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Levin, Matthew, 2000-2006 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - LeVine, Eric, 1994-2006 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Levine, George Ann and Steven, 1994-2001 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Levine, Jonathan, 1985-1996 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Levine, Sarabeth, 1989-1996 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Levine, Steven, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Levinsohn, Al, undated (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Leviton, Michael, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Levinton, Steve, 1990-1997 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Levitz, Norman, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Levy, Faye, 1991-1993 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Lewandowski, Stephen, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Lewis, Charles, 1990-1998 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Lewis, Dan, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Lewis, Edna, 1976-2006 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Lewis, Mair, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Lewis, Randy, 2001-2003 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Lewis, Rhys, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Lhulier, Robert, 1998-2002 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Lianides, Leon, 1987-1994 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Liccioni, Mary Beth, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Liccioni, Roland, 1997-2000 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Lichine, Alexis, undated (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Liebrandt, Paul, 2000-2006 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Liebert, Barbara, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Liebewohl, Abe, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Liebrandt, Paul, 2000-2006 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Light, Jill, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Liken, Kelly, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Lilly, Chris, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Limitone, Brian, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lindh, Kenneth, 1989-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Lindlbauer, Wolfgang, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Lindsay, Geoff, 1994-2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ling, Chin and Richard Hughes, 1985-1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lingle, Ken, 2006 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Link, Donald, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Linquist, Scott, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Linxe, Robert, 1983-1994 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Lipp, Michael, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Lippin, Jay, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Lippman, Marc, 1995-2005 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Lipsmeyer, Ken, 1993-1996 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Litman, Jim, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Little, Wendy, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Littlefield, Wendy and Don Feinberg, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Littman, Ryan, 2006-2007 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Liu, Guy, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Liu, Tony, 2004-2006 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Ljubicic, Angelo, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Llorca, Alain, 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Lo, Anita, 1993-2007 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Lo, Philip, 1991-2004 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Lock Hack, Jim, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Lockard, Michael, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - The Lodge, 2003-2005 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - LoDuca, Paul, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Logan, Andrew, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Logan, Nathan, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Lohninger, Mario, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Loiseau, Bernard, 1992-2003 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Lombardi, Antonio, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Lombardo, Lindo, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - LoMenyo, Mario, undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Lomonaco, Michael, 1991-2006 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Long, Cynthia, 1995-2001 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Long, Robert, 1986-1994 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Longo, Christina, undated (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Longo, Nancy, 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Looi, Peng, 1996-2003 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Lopata, William, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Loperfido, Donato, undated (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Lopez, Bruno, 1995-2003 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Lopez, Jaime, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Lopez, Julia, undated (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Lord, Melissa, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - LoSasso, Dewey, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Lotti, Sandra, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Loubier, Emanuel, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Loughhead, Willis, 1998-2001 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Loughran, John, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Louym Catherine de Zagon, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Love, Norman, undated (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Love, Tim, 2001-2006 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Lovell, Jay, 1999-2002 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Lozada-Hissom, Yasmin, undated (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Luc, Jean, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Luce, Keith, 1996-2002 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Lucero, Sheila, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Luchetti, Emily, 1991-2004 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Lucky's Tomatoes, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Ludvigsen, Wayne, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Ludwig, Fabian, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Lueck, Chris, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Luengas, Arnold, undated (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Lui, Andy, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Lui, Po, undated (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Luizza, Annette, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Luongo, Pino, 1993-2002 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Lupo, Maria Giordano, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Lusardi, Mark, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Lussier, Michele, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Lutey, Scott, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Lutz, Vid, 1996-2001 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Lycon, Jeremy, 2006-2007 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Lydon, Amanda, undated (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Lyle, Stephen, 1984-2003 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Lyman, Matt, 2001-2003 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Lynch, Barbara, 1994-2005 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Lynch, Louis, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Lynch, Reinhardt, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Lyster, Michele, 1987-1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Maccioni, Sirio, 1991-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Macdonald, Kevin, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - MacGowan, Robert, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Machado, David, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Mackenzie, Brian, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Macke, Leslie, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - MacLauchlan, Andrew, undated (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - MacMilan, Beau, 2004-2006 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - MacNeil, Dennis, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - MacPherson, Grant, 1993-2006 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Macquet, Dominique, 1995-2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Madani, Gerard, 1999-2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Madsen, Kim, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Madura, Jeffrey, 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Maeda, Seiji, 1989-1994 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Mafrici, Mauro, 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Maggiore, Tomaso, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Maguire, Kevin, 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Maguire, Neven, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Mahaffey, George, 1987-1999 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Maher, Christopher, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Mahoney, Keith, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Maillard, Erik, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - The Maine Event 2006, 1997-2006 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Majer, Christopher, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Makison, Jim, 1994-1998 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Malasky, Mary, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Malet-DuPont, Bernard Yves, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Malgeieri, Nick, 1989-2005 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Mali, Adam, 2003-2005 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Malik, John, 1998-2004 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Mall, Jeff, 2002-2005 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Mallaman, Francis, 2000-2002 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Maloney, Jennifer, 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Malouf, Waldy, 1987-2007 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Mammano, Jamie, 1997-2001 (Box 27, Folder 38a)
  - Man, Sun-Dao, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 38b)
  - Mancais, Ian David, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Mandel, Abby, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Mander, Helena Carratala, 1995-1997 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Maneet, undated (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Manfredi, Joseph, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Mangan, Luke, 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Mangrum, Terrie, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Maniere, Jacques, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Mann, Eric, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Mannino, Steve, undated (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Mannke, Joe, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Manrique, Laurent, 1977-2004 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Manning, Christopher, 2006-2007 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Manovich, Pamela, undated (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Mansfield, Brian, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Mantuano, Tony, 1984-2007 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Manzare, Joseph, 1993-2003 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Manzi, Antonia, undated (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Manzke, Walter, 2001-2004 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Maras, Gerard, 1991-1994 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Marcato, Luca, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Marcattilii, Valentino, undated (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Marcelli, Bob, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Marchesan, Claudio, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Marchesi, Gaultiero, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Marchetto, Silvano, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Marci, Fernando, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Marcon, Fabrice, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Marcatto, Luca, undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Marcotte, Kenneth, 1988-1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Marcus, Joe, 1980-2005 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Mardach, Anthony, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Marder, Bruce, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Maresca, Tom, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Margerum, Doug, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Margolis, Robert, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Marhencke, Ralf, 1990-1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Mariani, John, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Marineau, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Marinelli, Bill, 1990-1997 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Marini, Anthony, undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Marino, Salvatore, 1996-2006 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Marletta, Carmine, 1996-2002 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Marmulstein, Harold, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Marquet, Jean-Pierre, 1988-1993 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Marquise, Jeffrey, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Marricino, Paola, 1987-2004 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Marsella, Steven, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Marshall, David, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Marshall Fields, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Marshall, Jeremy and Jennifer, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Martelli, Marco, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Martello, Daniel, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Martin, David, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Martin, Eric, 1995-2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Martin, Gun, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Martin, Jim, 1994-2000 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Martin, Patrick, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Martinez, Daisy, 2005-2007 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Martinez, Marilu Madueno, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Martinez, Zarela, 1987-2006 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Marohue, Michael, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Martorella, Francesco, 1990-2006 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Marts, Carl, 1997-2000 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Marzovilla, Nicola, undated (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Mason, Eric, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Mason, Robert, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Mason, Susan, 1997-2004 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Masraff, George, undated (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Massie, Brian, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Master, Melvin, 1985-2003 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Masterton, Donnie, 1994-1998 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Mastronardi, Nicola, 1997-1999 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Matalon, Ahron and Shaul Natan, 1990-1993 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Matarese, Giuliano, 2000-2005 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Mather, Joshua, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Mathieson, Jon, 1994-1999 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Matmati, Rad, 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Matney, Eddie, 1993-2000 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Matsuhisa, Nobu, 1991-2001 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Matsusaka, Kazuto, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Matt, Peter, undated (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Mattei, Manuel, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Mattern, Mark, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Matthews, Larry, 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Matthews, Ronni, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Matthews, Sara, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Mattioli, Joseph, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Mattson, Cory, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Maufox, Vincent, 1989-1993 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Mauk, Benjamin, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Maurais, Ghyslain, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - Maury, Jean-Phillippe, 2000-2005 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - Mavrothalassitis, George (1 of 2), 1993-2006 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - Mavrothalassitis, George (2 of 2), 1993-2006 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Maws, Tony, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Max, Dennis, 1985-1988 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Max, Dean James, 1996-2006 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - Maxwell, Matthew, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - May. Mark, undated (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - May, Tony, 1990-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Maynard, Brett, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Maytan, Paul, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mazzanti, Chris, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Mazzi, Gian Piero, 1999-2002 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Mazzocca, Alex, 1994-2002 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mazzon, Maurizio, 1989-2002 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - McArthur, Sally, 1989-1995 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - McBride, Brian, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - McBride, Shane, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - McCabe, Paul, 2000-2004 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - McCaffree, Vivky, 1996-2004 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - McCalman, Max, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - McCann, David, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - McCarley, Pat, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - McCarthy, Gregg, 1991-2003 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - McCarthy, Jay, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - McCarthy, Peter, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - McCarthy, Roy, undated (Box 29, Folder 19a)
  - McCarty, Michael, 1989-2004 (Box 29, Folder 19b)
  - McCaw, Tim, 2005-2007 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - McCelvey, David, 1993-1996 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - McClain, Shawn, 1994-2002 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - McClain, Steven, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - McClellan, Todd, 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - McClelland, Frank, 1985-2001 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - McClure, Jason, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - McCord, Samuel, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - McCorkle, Krista, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - McCown, Sue, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - McCreight-Lindeborg, Susan, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - McCrery, Alex, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - McDavid, Jack, 1988-1994 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - McDevitt, James and Stacy, 1998-2001 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - McDonald, James, 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - McEachern, Tom, 1998-2002 (Box 29, Folder 35)